http://www.claret.org/en/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is: http://www.claret.org
Registration on this website is exclusively for Perpetually Professed members of the Congregation of Missionaries, Sons of the Immaculate Heart of Mary (Claretian Missionaries).
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
Only members of the Congregation can leave comments for they are the only ones who have access to the private part of the website. When they leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Data that you enter in the contact forms goes to the email of the Congregation but the email of the sender is kept hidden unless responded. All mails goes to spam so every 30 days the data you entered in the forms are deleted. You may ask for the deletion of your message even if the 30 days is not yet over.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
For non-claretians, we do not share your data to anyone since only data of Claretians are saved on this site.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
If you have asked for an account on this website, that means you are a perpetually professed member of the Congregation. We do not share your data unless given permission or the General asks for it.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
If you are a Claretian, your contact information is saved in website. If you happen to leave the Congregation, you may ask for the deletion of your contact information from this site.
Additional information
How we protect your data
For registered Claretians, your data are kept for the Claretians’ eyes only.
News CategoriesNews Categories
Select Category
25th and 50th Anniversaries
ACLA
Cameroun
Congo
East Nigeria
Mãe da África
October 2007
The Claretian Community “Claret”
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gF1sqohLLVQ NEWS FROM THE PRESSComunidad Terapúetica "Transforma tu vida": un modelo claretianoPresentación del libro “Lo que el Espíritu ha unido”Perpetuo Socorro organiza una mesa redonda virtual para presentar 'Lo que el Espíritu ha unido'Adiós al obispo sonriente, este sábado será su despedida en Mondoñedo5 Clochard collaboreranno alla cura degli spazi verdi del I Municipio
iClaret YouTube Channelhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BeGD_Lg473w General Postulation
General Prefecture of Formation Claretian Year
Proclade International Portal Biblico
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thanks
